

SWAROOP CHAKRABORTY

SOFTWARE PROFESSIONAL

# CONTACT

direct +91 983 13 05667 email ayanchax9088@gmail.com West Bengal,India

## PROFILE

Experienced software and IT professional carrying a total work experience of over 7 years with legitimate proficiency in Java EE, Spring(Boot), Rails, JPA & Hibernate Frameworks, Microsoft SQL, MySQL, Powershell Development, US HealthCare(Soarian Financials) Software Domain, HL7 Standards, User Interface Development with Classical JS, ReactJS, AngularJS & Bootstrap.

# EXPERIENCE

# ASSOCIATE SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER CERNER CORP | SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT



SOFTWARE ENGINEER | SEP 2018 - SEP 2019 TEST AUTOMATION ENGINEER | MAR 2018 - SEP 2018 TEST ANALYST | SEP 2017 - MAR 2018 SR. TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER | SEP 2016 - SEP 2017 TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER | FEB 2015 - SEP 2016

SYSTEM ENGINEER
SIEMENS AG | SEP 2014- FEB 2015



SOFTWARE DEVELOPER
ZANTRIK INC | AUG 2013- AUG 2014
SOFTWARE INTERN
AMTRON LTD | JAN 2013- JUN 2013





# EDUCATION

#### MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

GAUHATI UNIVERSITY | 2010-2013 GPA: 8.4

## DOMAIN EXPERTISE

- Core & Advanced Java/J2EE
- · Microsoft SQL
- MySQL
- .NET 3.5/4.0 | Powershell
- PHP/ASP/JSP/RubyOnRails
- US Financial HealthCare Systems(Soarian Financials)
- Java FX
- · REST Micro-services
- Spring MVC/Boot
- Bootstrap/JavaScript/React-JS - UI Development
- Maven/Gradle/Ivy
- Health Level 7(HL7)

## AWARDS

#### **CERNER MASTER TITLE**

HONOR FOR AUTOMATION EXCELLENECE FEBRUARY 2018 KANSAS CITY MISSOURI EVENT

#### **CERNER NIGHT IN TOWN HONOR FOR ABOVE & BEYONDS**

APR 2015 | JUN 2016 | AUG 2017 | JUN 2018 | FEB 2019 | JAN 2020 | JUL 2020

# INTERESTS

Music, Writing, Cricket, Feluda



